{"9":{"id":9,"question_name":"Design Patterns","question_text":"Who invented first The Design Patterns in computer programing? (Nickname, small caps)","question_type":"complete_text","number_of_answers":"","valid_answer":" gang of four","date":"2016\/04\/25 04:55:09pm "},"10":{"id":10,"question_name":"Investigate Class Scope PHP","question_text":"Which functions returns the current class Scope in php? [small caps, format = function_name()]","question_type":"complete_text","number_of_answers":"","valid_answer":" get_declared_classes()","date":"2016\/04\/25 04:55:22pm "},"11":{"id":4,"question_name":"Web Browsers","question_text":"Which of the following are Web Browsers?","question_type":"multiple_choice","number_of_answers":"4","valid_answer":null,"answer_1":"Mozilla Firefox","valid_answer_1":"on","answer_2":"Google Chrome","valid_answer_2":"on","answer_3":"Archicad","valid_answer_3":null,"answer_4":"Safari","valid_answer_4":"on","date":"2016\/04\/20 02:20:38pm "},"12":{"id":12,"question_name":"What Does OOP stands for","question_text":"What does OOP stand for in computer programing?","question_type":"single_choice","number_of_answers":"3","valid_answer":"valid_answer_2","answer_1":"Object Oriented Project","valid_answer_1":null,"answer_2":"Object Oriented Programming","valid_answer_2":null,"answer_3":"Oliver Owen Patrick","valid_answer_3":null,"date":"2016\/04\/25 06:24:43pm "},"13":{"id":6,"question_name":"Polymorphism definition","question_text":"What is Polymorphism in OOP?","question_type":"single_choice","number_of_answers":"3","valid_answer":"valid_answer_1","answer_1":"the process of creating several objects from specific base classes","valid_answer_1":null,"answer_2":"process of animal morphing","valid_answer_2":null,"answer_3":"this process doesn't exists","valid_answer_3":null,"date":"2016\/04\/20 02:22:09pm "},"14":{"id":7,"question_name":"Arhitectul Saggradei Familia","question_text":"Catedrala Saggrada Familia din Barcelona a fost proiectata de ?","question_type":"single_choice","number_of_answers":"3","valid_answer":"valid_answer_2","answer_1":"Corbusier","valid_answer_1":null,"answer_2":"Gaudi","valid_answer_2":null,"answer_3":"Gigi Becali","valid_answer_3":null,"date":"2016\/04\/21 02:39:41pm "},"15":{"id":7,"question_name":"CGI stands for...","question_text":"What does CGI stands for?","question_type":"single_choice","number_of_answers":"3","valid_answer":"valid_answer_3","answer_1":"Call George In","valid_answer_1":null,"answer_2":"Common Get Interface","valid_answer_2":null,"answer_3":"Common Gateway Interface","valid_answer_3":null,"date":"2016\/04\/28 02:56:29pm "},"16":{"id":8,"question_name":"Pluto","question_text":"Pluto este o planeta?","question_type":"single_choice","number_of_answers":"2","valid_answer":"valid_answer_2","answer_1":"Da","valid_answer_1":null,"answer_2":"Nu","valid_answer_2":null,"date":"2016\/04\/28 03:07:25pm "},"17":{"id":9,"question_name":"Electric Castle Romania","question_text":"In care oras din ROmania se tine Festivalul de muzica Electric Castle?","question_type":"multiple_choice","number_of_answers":"4","valid_answer":null,"answer_1":"Brasov","valid_answer_1":null,"answer_2":"Cluj-Napoca","valid_answer_2":null,"answer_3":"Bucuresti","valid_answer_3":null,"answer_4":"Bontida","valid_answer_4":"on","date":"2016\/04\/28 03:10:37pm "},"18":{"id":10,"question_name":"Php valid tags","question_text":"Which of the following are valid tags in php?","question_type":"multiple_choice","number_of_answers":"4","valid_answer":null,"answer_1":"<?php ... ?>","valid_answer_1":"on","answer_2":"<?= ... ?>","valid_answer_2":"on","answer_3":"<php ....>","valid_answer_3":null,"answer_4":"<php> ..<\/php.>","valid_answer_4":null,"date":"2016\/04\/28 03:14:24pm "},"19":{"id":11,"question_name":"Global Data Storage variable PHP","question_text":"The superglobal array which contains session storage data is :","question_type":"complete_text","number_of_answers":null,"valid_answer":"$_SESSION","date":"2016\/04\/28 03:20:11pm "}}